http://www.calhealth.org/general-information/privacy-policy

CAHHS/CHA is committed to protecting information disclosed
through this website. Your use of this website, or any inquiry or
comment you send, may be disclosed to CAHHS/CHA affiliates and
authorized entities solely to advance the mission and purpose of
CAHHS/CHA.
USE OF INFORMATION
The information you provide is used to respond to your comment or
inquiry and to provide various services to you.
NOTICE
This website collects information about your browser type,
browser version, operating system and IP address, which is
technical information shared by your browser automatically. We
also collect information on which documents you request and the
pages you view at this site. We keep personal information on the
identity of an individual visitor if you or your company has
provided the information at any time whether provided
electronically, in writing or verbally.
SECURITY
Any transmission you make on the Internet is not secure.
Therefore, you should always be concerned about any personally
identifiable information that you submit on the Internet.
PERSONAL IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
We collect personally identifiable information. We may ask for
your name, street address, city, county, state, zip code, e-mail
address and may request your telephone number. In the case of
mailing lists, we will ask for your e-mail address. If you make a
purchase we will ask for your credit card number or bank account
information. You are able to unsubscribe at any time from a
mailing list.
Personally identifying information includes, but is not limited
to, your:
CHOICE
We do not require that you register for general access to our
website. We collect any personally identifiable information from
any information you or your company submit or otherwise provide
to us and the information automatically provided by your browser.
If you choose to register as a member or advocate, to sign up for
one of our mailing lists, your registration information will be
permanently stored and used. Your registration information may be
added to or combined with other personally identifiable
information that we have already collected.
ACCESS
If you sign up for one of our mailing lists and decide to
unsubscribe, your information will not be deleted from our
servers, but your e-mail address will be removed from the mailing
list.
COOKIES
Cookies are small text files placed on your computer that are
used to identify you, often without your knowledge, while
visiting certain sites on the Internet. For example, cookies are
used by some sites to greet you personally, to post a list of
your favorite books to purchase, to remember what you had in your
shopping basket the last time you visited.
When using this website, cookies will be placed on your computer.
The cookies are used to facilitate the interaction between you
and our web pages. These cookies are used to collect or store
information on you and track you if you return to our website.
The cookies are permanent and will not be deleted when you exit
your browser.
You can prevent cookies from being placed on your computer by
accessing your browser’s preferences menu and deleting existing
cookies. There also are commercial programs available to help you
manage cookies. Before taking such steps, you should be aware
that some websites, including ours, will not work properly if you
choose to block the placement of cookies on your computer. You
will need to decide whether enabling cookies outweigh privacy
concerns.
CHANGES
Any changes in this privacy policy will be posted at least 30
days prior to the change taking effect. Any information collected
under this current policy will become subject to the terms of the
revised privacy policy when effective. All new information
collected, if any, would also be subject to the revised privacy
policy. An archive of previous policies is available on this
site.
CONTACT
If you have questions about this policy or feel that we have
acted in violation of this policy, please contact us or write us.
Volunteer Ambassadors' Club
Hospital TopicsCDPH Licensing & EnforcementAll Facilities Letters
Long-Term-Care Hospitals
Skilled-Nursing Facilities / Distinct Part Nursing Facilities
Subacute Care
Telemedicine & Telehealth
Women & Children
Construction / RenovationSeismic Mandate
CoverageCovered California MarketplaceCovered California Marketplace Resources
RHC Meeting Documents
Volunteer ServicesCommittee on Volunteer ServicesVolunteer Committees
CommitteesCommunications Committee
Case Management CommitteeCase Management Committee Documents
Managed Care Committee
Medication Safety CommitteeMedication Safety Committee Documents
January 1, 2018
CHA Corporate Partners:
Hospital Council of Northern and Central California Hospital Association of Southern California Hospital Association of San Diego and Imperial Counties Hospital Quality Institute
CHA is a member of:
American Hospital Association
Note: documents in Portable Document Format (PDF) require Adobe Acrobat Reader 5.0 or higher to view, download Adobe Acrobat Reader.
Have 10 minutes to help us improve our site?I'll do itNo thanks
